A Guide to the Genealogical Bureau of Virginia, 1923-1945
Library of Virginia
- Series II: Client files., Extent: 18 boxes. (Box 5-22)
  - Client file 140: Mrs. H. E. Ellett (family: Ellett, Pemberton, Mosby, Quarles, Spears) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Client file 141: Norman Call (family: Watt, Call, Hooper, Bacon, Clopton) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Client file 142: T. M. Smith (family: Smith, Boyce, Pettus) (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Client file 143: (family: Nelson, Daniel, Dabney) (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Client file 144: (family: Anderson, Johnson) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 32 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Client file 145: Virginia S. White (family: Harrison, Randolph, Bracey, Bressie) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 33; Box 30, Folder 3 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Client file 146: Julia Cottrell Collins (family: Cottrell, Collins, Hill, Crump, Walker, Drewry) (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Client file 147: Mrs. P. W. Turner (family: Wilson, Goodrich, Hines, Bolling, Drew) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 4 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Client file 148: Mrs. H. H. George (family: Coleman, Hampton, Pollard, Taylor) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 34 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Client file 149: Kenneth D. Steere (family: Duffield, Camp, Beard) (folder 1 of 2) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 5 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Client file 149: Kenneth D. Steere (family: Duffield, Camp, Beard) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Client file 150: Mrs. Horace Speed, Jr. (family: Alston, Jones, Hamlin) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 20 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Client file 150A: Tennie E. Vaden (family: Vaden, English, Jackson) Oversize item located in Box 26, Folder 35 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Client file 151: John Leigh Radcliffe (family: Radcliffe) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 21 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Client file 152: William E. Cox (family: Nelson) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 6 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Client file 153: Mrs. Charles H. Drane (family: Beaumont, Tillford, Gracey) (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Client file 154: Claude W. Johnson (family: Johnson, Walden, Fleming, Hughes, Parker, Mosby) (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Client file 155: J. B. P. Hill (family: Hill, Wells, Clayton) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Client file 156: Maben Jones (family: Hobson, Jones) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Client file 157: Edwin Wood Jordan (family: Wood, Jordan, Ball, Cheatham) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 1 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Client file 158: Mrs. M. G. Hart (family: Armistead, Dandridge, Meriwether, Anderson) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 2; Box 31, Folder 22 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Client file 159: F. D. Dent (family: Beverley, Dent, Sharp) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 3 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Client file 160: Edwin C. Wade (family: Wade) (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Client file 161: P. A. Seaton (family: Seaton, Bernard, Moore) (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Client file 162: Henry Watkins Ellerson (family: Chiles, Day, Todd, Walker, Ellerson) (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Client file 163: Mrs. Richard I. Manning (family: Anderson, Austin, Jackson, Johnson, Timberlake) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 23 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Client file 164: Mrs. H. J. Braden (family: Gilmer) (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Client file 165: Mason Britton (family: Britton, Poythress, Miller, Marks, Bolling, Wells) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 24 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Client file 166: W. F. Augustine (family: Chiles, Vaughan, Cobbs, Wyatt, Haley, Neal) (folder 1 of 2)Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 4; Box 31, Folder 25 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Client file 166: W. F. Augustine (family: Chiles, Vaughan, Cobbs, Wyatt, Haley, Neal) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Client file 167: M. F. Wooten (family: Wooten, Wooton) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 5 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Client file 168: W. E. Barret (family: Barret, Anderson) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 6 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Client file 169: Mrs. Donald C. Dickson (family: Jeter, Vaughan, Agee, Bright, Poythress, Tinsley) (folder 1 of 3) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 7 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Client file 169: Mrs. Donald C. Dickson (family: Jeter, Vaughan, Agee, Bright, Poythress, Tinsley) (folder 2 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Client file 169: Mrs. Donald C. Dickson (family: Jeter, Vaughan, Agee, Bright, Poythress, Tinsley) (folder 3 of 3) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Client file 170: Mrs. L. W. Gibbs (family: Willett, Van Cott, Betts, Williams) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 7 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Client file 171: Hibbert M. Weathers (family: Weathers) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 26 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Client file 172: Philip A. Terrell (family: Terrell) (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Client file 172A: Mrs. Montford Jones (family: Terrell, Burnley, Barksdale, Collier) (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Client file see 172 and 172A: (family: Terrell) (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Client file 173: Mrs. J. M. Richardson (family: Dickenson, Dickerson, Dukes) (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Client file 174: W. Mac. Jones (family: Jamestown residents) (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Client file 175: Lockwood Barr (family: Hawood, Sanders) (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Client file 176: Lucille Wales (family: Harrison, Rodgers) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 8 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Client file 177: (family: Johnson) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Client file 178: Mrs. Furnival, Mrs. Arthur W. Cannon (family: Waddill, Redwood) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 9 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Client file 179: Anna Jean Smith (family: Smith, Jefferson, Maclin) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Client file 180: Howard B. Weatherford (family: Weatherford) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 10 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Client file 181: Clara Buckner Dennis (family: Buckner) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 8 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Client file 182: Mrs. Sidney C. Probert (family: Hall) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Client file 183: Mrs. M. A. W. Gibbs (family: Skelton, Gifford, Crane, Davison) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Client file 184: George A. Dame (family: Dame, Green) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 11 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Client file 185: Mrs. W. J. Payne, Mrs. J. E. Warren (family: Cosby, Payne) (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Client file 186: B. L. Ancell (family: Key, Macon, Pettit) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 12 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Client file 187: Mrs. Fleming James O'Connor (family: Lewis) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 13 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Client file 188: Mrs. Nile Anderson (family: Massie, Wythe, Ballew) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 9 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Client file 189: Mrs. W. H. Lipford (family: Lipford) (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Client file 190: Mrs. Charles W. Byrd (family: Harrison) (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Client file 191: Mrs. J. L. Hand (family: Davenport) (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Client file 192: Mrs. Noah P. Sanderson (family: Hudson, Ferguson, Ingram) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 14 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Client file 193: Mrs. Louis Lee Judice, Edgar Bruce Ferguson (family: Ferguson, Godwin, Shelton, Collier) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 15; Box 31, Folder 27 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Client file 194: Mrs. Bruce V. Boxley (family: Boxley) (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Client file 195: Samuel Wilcox (family: Cocke, Goodman) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 16 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Client file 196: Eugene Massie (family: Massie, Walker, Smith, Thomson) (folder 1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Client file 196: Eugene Massie (family: Massie, Walker, Smith, Thomson) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Client file 197: Mrs. H. G. Swineford (family: Parker) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 28 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Client file 198: (family: Coleman, James) (folder 1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Client file 198: (family: Coleman, James) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Client file 199: Blake W. Meador (family: Meador) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 17 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Client file 200: Mrs. E. L. Williamson (family: Jackson) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 18 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Client file 201: Wright and Company (family: Drew, Selby, Trueheart, Carter, Colquitt) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 19 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Client file 202: (family: Pendleton, Eastwood, Dandridge, Henley) (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Client file 203: Will H. Daniel (family: Ivey, Johnson, Everett, Lawrence, West) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 20-21 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Client file 204: L. H. Jenkins (family: Jenkins) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Client file 205: (family: Moncure) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 22 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Client file 206: Walker Scott (family: Scott, Cheatham) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 23 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Client file 207: Lillian E. Harness (family: Harness) (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Client file 208: Mrs. Frank E. Jennings (family: Pendleton, Taylor, Crossthwait, Brockman, Collins, Terrell) (folder 1 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Client file 208: Mrs. Frank E. Jennings (family: Pendleton, Taylor, Crossthwait, Brockman, Collins, Terrell) (folder 2 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Client file 208: Mrs. Frank E. Jennings (family: Pendleton, Taylor, Crossthwait, Brockman, Collins, Terrell) (folder 3 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Client file 208: Mrs. Frank E. Jennings (family: Pendleton, Taylor, Crossthwait, Brockman, Collins, Terrell) (folder 4 of 4) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Client file 209: Mrs. J. McCurtice (family: Selby, Scarborough) (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Client file 209: Mrs. J. McCurtice (family: Selby, Scarborough) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 10 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Client file 210: Julien Harrison Hill (family: Harrison, Hill) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 24 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Client file 211: Charles Smith Caffery (family: Caffery) (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Client file 212: Charles Hill Jones (family: Jones) (folder 1 of 2) (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Client file 212: Charles Hill Jones (family: Jones) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 11 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Client file 213: Mrs. G. C. Montgomery (family: Jacobs, Peale) (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Client file 214: William Henry Carley (family: Carley) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 25 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Client file 215: (family: Leavell) (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Client file 216: Mrs. Robert Lee Warren (family: Warren, Chambliss, Smith) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 26 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Client file 217: Peter G. Cosby (family: Cosby, Woodson, Cocke) (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Client file 218: K. S. Loving (family: Loving) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 27 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Client file 219: J. Adger Stewart (family: McClanahan, Thoms, Green) (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Client file 220: Mrs. J. Porter Hines (family: Nichols) (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Client file 221: Mrs. W. A. Schmidt (family: Fore, Elliott) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 28 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Client file 222: Mrs. F. L. Seely (family: Grove, Harris, Taggott, Deane, Moore, Love, Jordan, Cosby) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 29 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Client file 223: Mrs. Charles P. Selden (family: Selden) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 12 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Client file 224: Mrs. Robert H. Tally (family: Chalkley, Ferguson, Holland) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 29 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Client file 225: Mrs. H. B. Frischkern (family: Hardwick[e], Ladd) (folder 1 of 2) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 30 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Client file 225: Mrs. H. B. Frischkern (family: Hardwick[e], Ladd) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Client file 225A: Robert E. Hardwicke (family: Hardwicke, Terrell, Moorman, Johnson) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 31 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Client file 226: Mrs. Willis P. Johnston (family: Bullock, Gordon, Hawkins, Henley) (folder 1 of 2) Oversize item located in Box 30, Folder 13 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Client file 226: Mrs. Willis P. Johnston (family: Bullock, Gordon, Hawkins, Henley) (folder 2 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Client file 227: Mrs. F. K. Perrow (family: Thompson) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 32 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Client file 228: Claude M. Terrell (family: Terrell, Lewis) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 33; Box 31, Folder 30 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Client file 229: Mrs. Robert L. Page (family: Page) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Client file 230: Mrs. F. A. Fernald, Mrs. Berton E. Beem (family: Cuyler, Brown, Huddleston, Fowler) (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Client file 231: Mrs. William Jefferson Payne (family: Payne, Cosby) (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Client file 232: Walter J. Sherman (family: Holt) (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Client file 233: Charlotte S. Driskell (family: Mayo) (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Client file 234: Mrs. H. M. Nelson (family: Nelson, Harris, Eldridge) (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Client file 236: T. Catesby Jones (family: Jones, Day, Chiles)Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 34 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Client file 301: Mrs. P. C. Mills (family: Grigg, Jones) (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Client file 302: G. M. Stafford (family: Jeter) Oversize item located in Box 31, Folder 31 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Client file 303: Mrs. Orton A. Kirschman (family: Short) (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Client file 304: Herman P. Williams (family: Williams) (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Client file 305: Mrs. Homer L. Ferguson (family: Anderson) Oversize item located in Box 27, Folder 35 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Series III: General records., Extent: 1 box. (Box 23)
  General records consist of abstracts of marriage records, notes, and other materials regarding the work of the Bureau.
  - Miscellaneous genealogical notes (family: Massie, Osborne) (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Marriage records from the Hustings Court of the City of Richmond, 1800-1850 (typescript compilation) (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Marriage bond abstracts from Hustings Court of Richmond, 1802-1813, also some Hanover marriages, September 1924 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Richmond City marriage bonds compilation (with some emancipation deeds), 1789-1807 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Cover for marriage records city of Richmond compilation (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Chesterfield County marriage records compilation, 1793-1819 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Marriage records from Halifax and Louisa Counties (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Middlesex County, Virginia, marriage records compiled by the Genealogical Bureau of Virginia (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Various county records--Augusta, Botetourt, Hanover, King George, Middlesex, Orange, Richmond, York, and Kentucky (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - W. Mac. Jones notebook (1 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - W. Mac. Jones notebook (2 of 3) (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - W. Mac. Jones notebook, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - List of charts (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Index to Quaker records of Nansemond County (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - A Kin Study by John Eacott Manahan of Scottsville, Virginia (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous papers (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Series IV: Non-Bureau records., Extent: 1 box. (Box 24)
  Non-Bureau records consist of papers of the Cobbs Hall Chapter of the Daughters of the American Revolution, including Bible records, biographies, and grave sites of members and Revolutionary War soldiers; correspondence of Jane Parker of Richmond regarding genealogy and the Mary Ball Memorial Museum and Library; articles; notes; and miscellaneous papers.
  - Cobbs Hall Chapter (DAR) Genealogical Records Committee reports and papers, 1972-1980, including Grandparent Project papers (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Cobbs Hall Chapter (DAR) correspondence, 1978-1979, including Grandparent Project (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Cobbs Hall Chapter (DAR) Bible records, Chilton family genealogy, John Mavity autobiography (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Cobbs Hall Chapter (DAR) Within the Court House at Lancaster (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Cobbs Hall Chapter (DAR) graves of DAR members marked, 1977-1980 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Cobbs Hall Chapter (DAR) graves of Revolutionary War soldiers marked (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Heraldica (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Jane Parker correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Articles and clippings (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous notes and papers (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Blank census forms and genealogical records forms (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Oversize materials., Extent: 7 boxes. (Box 25-31)
  Boxes contain oversized materials of the collection. Oversize materials are correlated to boxes and folders in Family Files and Client Files.